molo.me 2014-02-09

# MOLOME™

**MOLOME™**

**Privacy Policy (April 2011)**

Our privacy policy explains how personal information is collected, used and disclosed by MOLOME with respect to your access and use of our website located at MOLO.ME and MOLOME's social networking services (available via website and applications).

Our privacy policy may be modified from time-to-time. We will alert you that changes have been made by indicating on our privacy policy the date it was last updated.

**What Is Personal Information?**

"Personal information" means information that specifically identifies an individual (such as a name, address, telephone number, mobile number or e-mail address) or information about that individual that is directly linked to personally identifiable information. Personal information does not include "aggregate" information, which is data we collect about the use of our application, website and our services. Our privacy policy does not restrict or limit our collection and use of aggregate information.

**What Personal Information Do We Collect?**

We actively collect certain information you voluntarily provide to us, such as when you create an account and profile, send us an email or post information or other content to our site.

We automatically collect certain information when you use our application, website and our services, such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address, your operating system, your phone model, the browser type, network and connectivity information, location information, the address of a referring site and your activity on our website and applications. We treat this information as personal information if we combine it with or link it to any of the identifying information mentioned above. Otherwise, it is used in the aggregate only.

We may also automatically collect certain information through the use of "cookies" or web beacons.

**How Do We Use the Personal Information We Collect?**

We use personal information collected through our site and our services for the purposes described in our privacy policy or elsewhere on our site. For example, we may use personal information we collect:

• to provide our services or information you request, and to process and complete any transactions;

• respond to your emails, submissions, questions, comments, requests, and complaints and provide customer service;

• to monitor and analyze site usage and trends, and to personalize and improve our site and our users’ experiences on our site, such as providing ads, content, or features that match their profiles or interests, and to increase our site's functionality and user friendliness;

• to send you confirmations, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages and otherwise facilitate your use of, and our administration and operation of, our site; and

• for any other purpose for which the information was collected.

**What Personal Information Do We Share With Third Parties?**

We will not share the personal information we collect from you through our site or our services with third parties, except as described in our privacy policy or on our site. For example, we share personal information as follows:

• with service providers who are working with us in connection with the operation of our site or our services;

• when you give us your consent to do so, including if we notify you on our site that the information you provide will be shared in a particular manner and you provide such information;

• when we believe in good faith that we are lawfully authorized or required to do so or that doing so is reasonably necessary or appropriate to comply with the law or legal processes or respond to lawful requests or legal authorities, including responding to lawful subpoenas, warrants or court orders;

• to enforce or apply our privacy policy, our terms of use or our other policies or agreements; and

• in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition, or in any other situation where personal information may be disclosed or transferred as one of the business assets of us.

We are not responsible for the actions of service providers or other third parties, nor are we responsible for any additional information you provide directly to any third parties.

**Links to Other Sites**

Our site may contain links to other sites. Any personal information you provide on the linked pages is provided directly to that third party and is subject to that third party's privacy policy. Our privacy policy does not apply to such linked sites, and we are not responsible for the content or privacy and security practices and policies of these sites or any other sites that are linked to from our site.

**What Steps Do We Take To Protect Your Information Online?**

We take reasonable measures to protect your personal information in an effort to prevent loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. Please be aware, however, that despite our efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable and no method of data transmission can be guaranteed against any interception or other type of misuse.
